You can't paint over the truth.
The Burnt Orange Heresy is a mystery, thriller, crime
film directed by Giuseppe Capotondi.
Hired to steal a rare painting from one of the most enigmatic painters of all time, an ambitious art
dealer becomes consumed by his own greed and insecurity as the operation spins out of control.
James Figueras, played by Claes Bang.
Berenice Hollis, played by Elizabeth Debicki.
Joseph Cassidy, played by Mick Jagger.
Jerome Debney, played by Donald Sutherland.
Evelina Macri, played by Rosalind Halstead.
Rodolfo, played by Alessandro Fabrizi.
The Burnt Orange Heresy is a 2019 crime thriller film directed by
Giuseppe Capotondi and with a screenplay by Scott Smith.
The film is based on the book of the same name by Charles Willeford and stars
Claes Bang, Elizabeth Debicki, Mick Jagger, and Donald Sutherland.
The Burnt Orange Heresy was selected as the closing film at the 76th Venice International
Film Festival and was released on March 6, 2020, by Sony Pictures Classics.
The film explores themes of con man, murder, art, painter as artist, malicious.
The tone is intense and mind_bending.